medievaltimes.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Medieval Times Dinner & Tournament

At Medieval Times Entertainment, we respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy covers how we collect, store, use, disclose, and transfer information we may collect from you when you visit our website or communicate with us through this website. Please familiarize yourself with our Privacy Policy, and review it periodically. Medieval Times may update its Privacy Policy from time to time.

**Collection of Personal Information**

We may ask you to provide personal information through this website which may identify you. Medieval Times may share this personal identifying information with its affiliates. Medieval Times and its affiliates may also combine the personal information you supply on this website with other information to provide and improve our services, content, and advertising. You are not required to provide the personal information we request; however, if you chose not to provide the information, we may be unable to provide you with the services you request, and we may be unable to respond to your communications.

By way of example, when you purchase tickets on our website, you may be asked to provide personal information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and payment or credit card information. When purchasing tickets, you also have the opportunity to sign up for periodic emails concerning events in your area or entertainment offers.

Likewise, you may be asked to provide personal information in response to our customer surveys, sweepstakes, or contests, when you request to join our Birthday Fellowship, or when you request to participate in similar promotions.

**Use of Personal Information**

The personal information you provide allows us to provide ticket and other services to you. It also allows us to send you updates on events and entertainment offers from Medieval Times and our affiliates. If you do not want to be on our mailing list, you may opt out anytime by contacting us at one of the addresses listed in our Privacy Policy under “Controlling Your Information.”

We also use personal information to help us operate and improve our website, improve our services, products, and advertising, and for loss prevention and anti-fraud purposes. For example, we may use your personal information, including date of birth, to confirm you are not a minor or to provide age-appropriate services to you. We may also use personal information for internal purposes, including auditing, data analysis, and for communications with you. If you provide personal information for a customer survey, sweepstakes, contest, or to join our Birthday Fellowship or respond to similar promotions, we may use your personal information to administer those programs and other internal uses. We may also use information you provide us when carrying out a purchase transaction to track your purchases or fulfillment of your orders.

Occasionally, we may use your personal information to send important communications, including notices about your ticket purchases, changes to our privacy policies, or changes to our terms and conditions. Because this information is vital to your use of our website and your communications with us, you may not opt out of receiving those important communications.

**Collection of Non-Personal Information**

Like most website operators, Medieval Times collects non-personal identifying information. The data is not in a form which, on its own, identifies you. Examples of non-personal identifying information that we may collect or use include your browser type, operating system, the identity of the city from which you accessed our website, your ISP address, your ISP provider, and details of your visits to our website, including location data, the Medieval Times web pages that you visited, and the identity of the referral web pages you may have visited immediately before and after you visited our website. If we combine non-personal information with personal information, any combined information will be treated as personal information as long as it remains combined.

**Use of Non-Personal Information**

We collect non-personal identifying information to present our website and its contents to you, improve our website, deliver a better and more personalized service to you, estimate visitors to our website and usage patterns, deliver targeted promotions and advertising, measure the effectiveness of web searches, identify trends and customer preferences, recognize you when your revisit our website, gather aggregate information about our user base, provide banner and other advertising on third party websites concerning our products and services to you, and for internal purposes. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, Medieval Times does not share this information with third parties.

**The Technologies We Use in the Collection of Non-Personal Information**

The technologies we use for automatic data collection of non-personal information may include “cookies” and other technologies such as web beacons or pixel tags. Our goal in using these tools is to make your experience with Medieval Times more convenient and personal. For example, knowing that someone has used your computer or other device to search for tickets to a show at one of our castles helps make our advertising and email communications more relevant to your interests and helps us provide better customer service.

Most browsers automatically accept “cookies.” Our website does not respond automatically to “Do Not Track” requests from your browser. As a result, if you want to disable cookies on your device to avoid tracking, set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. Check with your browser provider for instructions. To disable our website placing cookies on your device, you must disable cookies on each browser you use to access our website. Please note that certain features of our website may not be available once cookies are disabled.

**Service Providers**

Medieval Times shares personal information with service providers and contractors we use to support our business. Those companies provide services such as processing or fulfilling customer orders, delivering tickets, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, processing information, conducting customer research, and providing web-based advertising concerning us or our affiliates on other websites you visit. The service providers are obligated to protect your personal information. The companies are located principally in the United States, and secondarily in Canada, but may also have servers or operations in other parts of the world.

At times, Medieval Times and its affiliates may also provide non-identifying personal information to service providers we use to deliver targeted advertisements concerning Medieval Times or its affiliates. Such information is shared to provide, improve, or advertise our products, services, and advertising, and is not shared with third parties for their own marketing purposes or for other parties to market their product or services.

**Other Disclosures**

On occasion, we may disclose your personal information to comply with a court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to a government or regulatory request from within or outside your country of residence. We may also disclose information about you if we conclude that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other matters of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate. Likewise, we may disclose information about you if we reasonably determine that disclosure is necessary or appropriate to enforce our Privacy Policy or our terms and conditions of website use. In the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale, we may also transfer any personal information to a buyer or other successor, including by way of liquidation or similar proceeding.

**Our Protection of Your Personal Information**

Medieval Times takes seriously the security of your personal information. When your personal information is stored by Medieval Times, we use a secure third-party data center in the United States with physical and electronic access restrictions and security measures designed to secure your information from accidental loss or unauthorized access, use, alteration, or disclosure. We reserve the right to move your data to a Medieval Times facility or other third-party data center in the United States or Canada, or in such other country as we may reasonably determine, provided such data center has appropriate physical and electronic access restrictions and security measures. The personal information we store may include, among other things, the type of credit card you utilized for transactions with us, but not credit card numbers or security codes processed by our service providers or credit processing firms. To better serve you, we retain transaction data from your ticket purchases, including but not limited to information concerning the size of your party, the date and type of transaction, the type of seats you purchased, and any promotional offer you utilized. We retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

**Children**

Medieval Times understands the importance of extra precautions to protect the safety and privacy of children. Our website is not intended for use by children. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from children under the age of 13, or from children under the equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, absent parental consent. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13, or other equivalent minimum age, without first receiving verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information as soon as possible. If you believe we might have information from or about such a child, please contact us at one of the addresses listed in our Privacy Policy under “Controlling Your Information.”

**Access to Other Websites**

This website may provide links to other websites not operated by Medieval Times Entertainment, Inc., including websites operated by affiliates of Medieval Times. This Privacy Policy does not apply to those other websites, nor does it apply to any unaffiliated third party's website such as Facebook or Google. Those websites have their own privacy policies that differ from ours. When you click on a link to those websites, or visit those other websites, you are entering another site. You should carefully review the privacy policies and terms and conditions of use of those sites, because those terms will apply to your visit to those sites.

**Your California Privacy Disclosures**

Our website is unable to respond to “Do Not Track” requests. If you want to disable cookies on your device, set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent, as described elsewhere in our Privacy Policy.

We do not share your personal information with non-affiliates except as described in this Privacy Policy. When we share personal information with our service providers, it is for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, and not to enable the service provider to market their services or the services of other than us and our affiliates.

**International Users**

This website is directed to visitors and potential visitors to our castles in the United States and our castle in Canada. This website is operated by Medieval Times Entertainment, Inc., a United States company, which is the controller with regard to your personal information. Information you provide from outside of the United States may be transferred or accessed by us in the United States and Canada, and in limited circumstances to our service providers who may also have a presence in other countries. We share your personal information only in the limited circumstances and for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Regarding Electronic Messages in Canada**

Medieval Times and its affiliates are [Canadian CASL compliant](http://fightspam.gc.ca/eic/site/030.nsf/eng/home) and do not intentionally send commercial emails to Canadian residents, other than to those who have opted-in to receive such emails Likewise, we do not intentionally send commercial emails to anyone who has opted out of emails by unsubscribing or requesting deletion by contacting us at the email or mailing addresses listed below, in “Controlling Your Information.”

**Controlling Your Information**

If you are receiving electronic mail or electronic messages from us, and you do not want to be on our mailing list, desire to withdraw a previously given consent to electronic messages, desire to opt out of our promotional emails, or have any questions concerning our Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacypolicy@medieval times.com, or write us at:

            Medieval Times Entertainment

            Privacy Policy Issues

            6363 N. Hwy. 161, Suite 400

            Irving, TX 75038

Please be sure to include your name, address, email address, and telephone number along with your request. To remove your name from an email list, you may also click on the “Unsubscribe” link at the end of the email.

You may also contact us at the addresses above if you desire to obtain access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided us. All such communications will be examined and replies issued where appropriate. We reserve the right to decline requests to modify or delete information that we are required to retain by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also decline requests to modify or delete records when the request is frivolous, jeopardizes the privacy rights of other users, is impractical to accomplish, or if the relevant jurisdiction does not require compliance with your request.

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy**

            This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect on this website, and to email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by us offline or through other means, including information collected on websites operated by third parties, whether or not those websites are linked to or accessible from our website. It is your choice whether to use our website. Your continued use of this site constitutes your acceptance of our Privacy Policy.

This Medieval Times Privacy Policy was last updated on January 12, 2016.
